<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><toc xmlns="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/webhelp/toc" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><title><span xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="title">Armando's Recipe Guide</span></title><topic href="c-breakfast.html" data-id="c-breakfast"><title>Breakfast Recipes</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc"> Welcome to breakfast at Marjan's! Today I have left a set of recipes for you to follow,   so that your experience this weekend is that much more easy and relaxing. The following recipes   will provide you with an energetic start to your day that will leave you satisfied until lunch!   After you have enjoyed your breakfasts, a clean-up guide can be found to help with the little or   big messes you may have made in your breakfast adventures. A troubleshooting and reference guide   have been included for your convenience. </p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="javascript:void(0)"><title>Side Dish</title><topic href="t-recipeone.html" data-id="t-hash"><title>Hearty Breakfast Hash</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">This colorful and flavorful hash is sure to provide everyone with an array of flavors         and tastes to satisfy any morning hunger. Ingredients are easily interchangeable, making         this recipe fun and dynamic.<img class="image" src="hash.jpg" /></p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic><topic href="javascript:void(0)"><title>Main Dishes</title><topic href="t-recipethree.html" data-id="t-wrap"><title>Southwest Breakfast Wraps</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">These wraps are portable and easy to share. Enjoy them while reading the morning         paper, getting ready for work, or over the breakfast table with loved ones. Packed with a         variet of ingrediets, these wraps are customizable and fun to make.<img class="image" src="wrap.jpg" /></p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="t-recipefour.html" data-id="t-cakes"><title>Quinoa Cakes</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">These crispy quinoa cakes are a twist on the traditional sausage patty found at         breakfast. These savory cakes are packed with fresh vegetables and will be great served hot         or room temperature. They are easily enjoyed alone or with a side of hash and a smoothie             <img class="image" src="patty.jpg" /></p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic><topic href="javascript:void(0)"><title>Beverages</title><topic href="t-recipetwo.html" data-id="t-smoothie"><title>Kale and Strawberry Smoothie</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">This smoothie is an easy breakfast that is full of all your essential nutrients for         the day. The healthy greens are hardly noticeable with the addition of naturally sweet         fruits. This is a great breakfast to make in a rush or to enjoy in the house on a slow         morning. <img class="image" src="smoothie.jpg" /></p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="t-chai.html" data-id="t-chai"><title>Chai Latte</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">This rich and robust drink is full of many herbs and spices that will warm up the         start to any day. Chai lattes are known for their comforting qualities and are easier to         make than taking a trip down to your local barista <img class="image" src="chai.jpg" /></p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic><topic href="javascript:void(0)"><title>References</title><topic href="t-references.html" data-id="references"><title>Recipe References</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">The recipes provided have been modified for each user. To learn more about the recipes         used in today's breafast guide, visit the following links below: <img class="image" src="sources.jpg" /><br /></p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic><topic href="javascript:void(0)"><title>Cleaning</title><topic href="t-clean.html"><title>Clean-up</title><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic></toc>